Sora-chan, this is it.
ソラちゃん、これです
copper?
どう?
Looks really delicious.
めっちゃ美味しそう
Look, doesn't this look great?
ほら、これめっちゃ映えじゃない?
Hey, it's beautiful.
ね、綺麗
So, shall we sit here?
じゃあ、ここ座っちゃう?
Well then, let's eat this together.
じゃあ、これ2人で食べよう
Is it okay to go first?
先っちょいいかな?
First?
先っちょ?
It's okay to go first.
先っちょいいよ
Isn't it good?
いいよね?
I couldn't get it at all.
全然取れなかった
Something like this?
こんなもん?
Yeah.
うん
delicious?
美味しい?
sweet.
甘い
It's insanely delicious.
めちゃめちゃ美味しい
good.
よかった
Today, I actually had a surprise.
今日ね、実はサプライズがあった
what?
何?
Well then, when I go to the beach later, I'll tell you.
じゃあ、後で海の方行ったら、教える
fun.
楽しみ
Wow, what a beautiful view.
わー、すごい景色、綺麗
hey.
ね
Yes, I have a present.
そうだ、プレゼントあって
what?
何?
Sarah, it was your birthday, right?
サラちゃん、誕生日だったでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
That's why I bought you a present today.
だから今日、プレゼント買ってきたんだ
Oh, really?
え、本当?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, I'm happy.
え、嬉しい
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってね
Yeah.
うん
thank you.
ありがとう
Try opening it.
開けてみてよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
Yeah.
うん
Try opening it.
開けてみてよ
What is it?
なんだろう?
I thought you'd be happy.
喜んでくれると思ってさ
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
cute.
可愛い
Well, it's cold so it's just right.
えー、寒いからちょうどいいね
yes.
そう
That's gloves.
それ、手袋
Eh, that's cute.
え、可愛い
Try it.
してみて
Which one?
どっちだ?
This way?
こっちか
No, I definitely think these gloves look good on me.
いや、絶対この手袋、俺、似合うと思うんだよね
Yeah.
うん
Wow, that's cute.
わー、可愛い
Hands are big.
手、おっきい
Hey, it's big.
ね、おっきい
warm.
温かい
Isn't there?
いないない?
I never lost my gloves.
手袋、いったんないない
Well then.
じゃ ーん
Please put it away for a while.
ちょっとしまってね
Sora-chan.
そらちゃん
Yeah.
うん
After this,
この後さ、
Don't go to all places at once.
一 気にの場所行かない
It's a cherry.
さくらんぼだよ
Yeah.
うん
That's fine, right?
いいでしょ
Yeah.
うん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Isn't this big?
これ、おっきいんじゃない?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Yeah.
うん
a little bit.
ちょっと
Yeah.
うん
cute.
可愛い
Looks like a cherry.
さくらんぼみたい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいじゃん
There are cherries here.
さくらんぼがある、ここに
You look the same, here.
お 揃いだね、こっちと
Matching?
お揃い?
It's just my imagination.
気のせいだよ
Is it just my imagination?
気のせい?
If you see it, you'll find out.
見 たらバレちゃうよ
I can't see it.
見えないもん
Can't you see it?
見 えない?
This is also a cherry on top.
これもさくらんぼじゃん
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いでしょ
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Aren't you in the mood?
こっち気分じゃないの?
this.
これ
It's still standing after all.
やっぱり立ってるじゃん
standing on the earth
地球に立ってる
Look, look, this.
ほ ら、ほら、これ
What is this?
これ何これ?
Did you see it?
見た?
Yeah.
うん
What is this?
なんだ、これ
Ecchi.
え っち
Naughty.
えっち
Hold your legs together like this, like this.
こうやって足一緒に持ってて、こうやって
yes?
そう?
Do you feel like this?
こうすると感じる?
Do you make that face?
そんな顔する?
Yeah.
うん
Too bad I can't see anything.
惜しいよ、何も見えない
I've never been seen.
見られたことないよ
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Amazing, beautiful.
すごい、綺麗
Do you like being licked?
舐められるの好き?
Yeah.
うん
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Will it become normal?
普通の前になってくる?
It's so embarrassing, I'm going to school.
すごい恥ずかしい、学校してる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Yeah.
うん
Where was it?
どこだった?
Butt.
お尻
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
It's so snappy.
すっげーぴちゃぴちゃだね
I also like to leave it like this.
こうやって置いとくのも好きなんだけど
good?
いい?
Leave it like this.
こうやって置いといて
Yeah.
うん
Pi-cha-picha, pants.
ぴ ちゃぴちゃ、パンツを
It's picha picha.
ぴちゃぴちゃだ
Yes, it's snappy.
うん、ぴちゃぴちゃだよ
It's picha picha.
ぴちゃぴちゃだよ
By the way, do you touch it like this?
ちなみに、こうやって触ったりするの?
Yeah.
うん
do not?
しない?
Yeah.
うん
That's the look on your face.
してるな、なんかその顔
You're doing it, right?
してるでしょ
No, right?
ないでしょ
Those eyes are amazing.
すげー目なんだ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
Yeah.
うん
Isn't there a special way to touch it?
こだわりの触り方とかないの?
There isn't.
ないよ
do not have?
ない?
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
Do you know that I'm falling asleep right now?
すぐ寝てるの分かる?
Yeah.
うん
fun.
楽しい
It's very narrow.
すごく狭い
Yeah.
うん
narrow.
狭 い
Yeah.
うん
I don't know.
わかんないよ
Sora-chan, I never thought the day would come when I would have my penis touched.
そらちゃん、おちんちん触ってもらう日が来るとは思わなかった
Yeah.
うん
Are you touching your penis?
おちんちん触ってるんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
so?
そんなに?
can?
できる?
Yeah.
うん
Yay!
やったー
Sora-chan, together.
そらちゃん、一緒に
My left hand is dick.
左手をちんちんさ
If you let Sora-chan do something like this,
そらちゃんにこんなことをさせるとさ、
I feel like I'm going to hit the nail on the head.
なんかバチ当たりそう
From the wall.
壁さまから
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
real?
ほ んと?
Yeah.
うん
well,
じゃ、
Chimonaberu today?
今日 ちもなべる?
Yeah.
うん
What do you have?
何がある?
Yeah.
うん
Does it look like this now?
今はこうやって見えるか
You're really good at it, I guess.
めっちゃ上手だね、なんか
Because I was familiar with it.
なれかったから
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
That feels good.
その気持ちいい
Yeah.
うん
It's amazing how far you can go.
すごい向こうまでくまいてる
Yeah.
うん
How far will you go?
どこまでやる?
That far?
そこまで?
Yeah.
うん
A lot of chimo?
ちもだいぶ?
Yeah.
うん
I'm going home.
帰るじゃん
My hole is throbbing.
おしい穴、ひきゆきしてる
This is what I've been wanting to add.
入れたくなってきたって、これ
Should I include it?
入れたほうがいいの?
Okay.
いいよ
Yeah.
うん
So, do you like bags?
それじゃん、バッグが好き?
Yeah.
うん
I haven't done much.
あんまりしたことない
That's right.
そうだよね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
bag.
バッグ
Have you ever done it?
やったことある?
do not have.
ない
That's right.
だよね
Why not try a little challenge?
ちょっとチャレンジしてみない?
Would you like to try the challenge?
チャレンジしてみる?
You're using what makes you feel good about yourself.
自分の気持ちいいところを対応に動かしてるじゃん
like this?
こう?
yes?
そう?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yeah.
うん
Aren't you an idol at school?
学校でアイドルなんじゃないの?
Maybe.
もしかして
Are you an idol?
アイドルでしょ?
It's different.
違うもん
That's right.
そうだな
It's true.
本当だよ
Shall I take it off?
脱いちゃおうか
feeling
気持
Is it okay?
ち いい?
Yeah.
うん
It feels good too.
こっちも気持ちいいんだよね
Your butt is really small.
お尻が小さいね、めっちゃ
Yeah.
うん
This one also has a big tail.
こっちも尻尾が大きいね
Yeah.
うん
Are you going to do that?
ってやるの?
Yeah.
うん
like.
好き
Let's take it off now.
もう脱いちゃおう
Let it all out inside.
中にいっぱい出して
warm?
温かい?
Yeah.
うん
Hey, do you understand that?
ちょっと、それの分かる?
Yeah.
うん
I was so happy.
め っちゃ 幸せだった
This one.
こっちが
Yeah.
うん
I was happy.
幸 せだった
You have to lick your own spirit.
自分の精神を舐めなきゃいけない
Completed.
完成で
surely.
確かに
Return to manga.
マンガに返して
Seino.
せーの
Good.
よいしょ
copper?
どう?
this.
これ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Hello.
こんにちは
Oh, the sound of sex.
あら、エッチの音
Naughty sounds.
エッチの音
Where is it?
どこでしょ?
What is that?
何それ?
Awesome.
すっげー
Which one feels better when using power outside?
外で使うパワーがどっちが気持ちいい?
But this one is better.
でも、こっちの方が
Is this better?
こっちの方がいい?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, it's falling apart.
うわ、崩れてきた
Wow.
うわー
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, your body is so soft.
わー、体柔らかいなね
It's super soft.
めっちゃ柔らかい
Wow.
うわー
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Is this better?
こ っちの方がいい?
Ah, the members' sweat.
あ、メンバーの汗が
Sweat?
汗が?
Yeah.
うん
This is really strong.
めっちゃ強いよ、これ
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
Maybe a little strong.
ちょっと強いかも
strong?
強い?
Yeah.
うん
Is this guy too strong?
こいつは強すぎる?
Too strong.
強すぎる
Too strong?
強すぎる?
Yeah.
うん
Guess what makes you feel good.
自分の気持ちいいとかを当てて
Yeah.
うん
Have it.
持ってて
like this?
こう?
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, it's so wet.
あー、びちゃびちゃびちゃびちゃ
It's so wet.
びちゃびちゃびちゃびちゃびちゃ
Amazing.
すごーい
I wiped a lot, again?
いっぱい拭いてきた、また?
Yeah.
うん
The pink middle?
ピンク色の真ん中?
Yeah.
うん
It's so wet.
びちゃびちゃびちゃ
Amazing illeryl.
すごいilleryl
Oh no.
やば
Let's go this way.
こっち行っちゃおう
Let's go.
行っちゃおう
Can I make you feel better?
気持ちよくしてもらおうかな?
I won't look at it because it's cute.
可愛いから見ちゃわないよ
This one too
こ っちも
I reacted.
反 応しちゃった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
tell me.
教えて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
One more time.
もう一回
I said it once.
一回言ったもん
One more time.
もう一回
spiteful
意地悪
Can I do that?
して いい?
Another one
もう 一
times.
回
One more time.
もう 一回